Okay, so I'm now recording, I'm going to share my screen with you so that I can
share the powerpoint.
There we go.
Okay, can we see that? Okay, everyone.
Yeah.
Okay, so welcome to our women of webcam call.
So we're hoping that we can, with this call, just give you some information to
go over some of the basics.
It'll be a good one for some of the newbies to come to you or to watch back.
Hopefully we can give you just a bit of information. Go over the basics in a
bit more detail.
And then we thought that we'd just open up the questions for us, our mentors
and anybody else that wants to answer the questions about.
Well, you'll see what they're about. There's two or three questions at the end,
and we can all just inspire each other and share our ideas.
And if we had just come away from this, you know, with one or two nuggets of
like things we can do to step up that game or, you know, switch our niche or
whatever else then, and then we're winning our way.
And so let's get into it.
Yeah, so let's do some introductions first then, shall we?
So if each of us want to answer this question, you know, no pressure if you don
't, if you don't feel like speaking.
But those of us that want to want to just say a little bit about how long we've
been coming.
And what does it do for you and how's it fit into your life.
So he's a couple of people coming in now.
Yes, go on.
I think trying to come for 10 years, but I've been pathetic. I've been pathetic
it coming. I'm not sitting there. I'm sure I did right to see about that.
And then about November.
I came into EC saying, and I love it now I've got into the comments to come
away from the effort and I find the common is much more interesting.
Then the physical side, because you can be creative, which has led me to be
creative for so full tell you.
We've literally, I've literally, I've literally inundated with like ideas and
it's like, well, I'm going to create this way and create that way.
And it gives you that opportunity to make that niche to actually get income
brought in, if that makes sense.
And I think with EC, it's motivated me to be more creative.
And I found since November, where I was making 10 credits a year prior on
comments.
But now I'm making more of these 361 credits in the last couple of weeks.
Yeah.
And that time it wasn't part time. That's not even full time. And I've got the
ties picked for me to come today and I still haven't gotten come yet. So I'm
done on time later on.
But yeah, you can be creative as much as I want, which I love. I think it's
brilliant.
But yeah, that makes sense. I think that was the question, wasn't it?
Yeah. Thank you. Thank you. It's nice to hear, you know, from a relatively new
person.
You're a familiar face now.
George, do you want to say a little bit about that? Yeah, sure.
And so I've been coming now for nearly nine years.
And what it does for me in my life and how I fit into my life.
Well, to be honest, I don't know what I'd be doing if I wasn't coming.
This has been my main in comfort all of that time. And yeah, I love it. It's
like, obviously, like, I love it so much. I want to like tell everyone about it
and like, you know, tell everyone how amazing it is because it's done so much
for my life.
And it allows me to basically have complete freedom and look after myself
always in all of these different countries and know that.
I've always got something that if I'm ever like really, really struggling, I
could just smash it out and sit on it like all day, every day for as long as
possible until I've, you know, saved up one of the leaders.
But I feel like it's not really got to that because I've come in, it's allowed
me to always feel good about my finances, you know, well, not always. It took
me some time to get to that point. Of course, but once I got there, it's always
it's been consistent since then.
So, yeah, I love it. I love coming and I'll always rave about it.
Yeah, amazing. I love hearing about it.
Oh, should I go. So, I have been coming for about five years.
What it's done for me is God so much. I mean, obviously financially, it took a
lot of pressure off me and it meant that I could leave, you know, jobs was
working till like one o'clock or two o'clock in the morning.
And then, and then like getting up to do the school run and like having a
toddler all day. So yeah, when I could leave that job I was really happy.
And so it's given me more time with the kids helped me like with my finances,
you know, being with two kids.
And it's helped me to study so that now I can, I've gone through all my studies
.
And it's always fitted into my life in different ways, I guess, at first, I
used to just used to go on in the evenings, like maybe three times a week and
then got more and more because I got a bit obsessed with it.
And then, yeah, over the years it's just like I've done different jobs or I've
done it full time.
But I think that's what one thing I love about it is that it doesn't matter
what your life looks like you can always fit it in.
So yeah, that's good.
Can I add to that a little bit?
Yeah.
It's my video on.
Oh, it was.
Yeah.
Can you see me?
Oh, yeah.
Sorry.
I'm a mess girl.
Sorry about that.
Lovely.
I've got a house for at the moment and that's how much this does fit in with
your life.
And I've got two children, they are 15 and seven.
At the moment, I've also got two, two year olds here and three women sitting in
the kitchen.
And like so supportive of this job and how much it's like completely
transformed my life.
Don't ever think if you're a mum that you can't do this or if you've got kids,
it's the wrong thing to do because it's 100%.
Like it has massively changed my life and it's meant that I can provide for my
children in ways I've never believed was possible.
My son's going skiing with his school next week.
The cost me a lot of money and I was able to do that for him with zero help
from anyone else.
It's just amazing and it fits in around them and they've been in school and
then go to bed at night and, you know, not having to.
I can literally work at night. Again, my son is 15. So he doesn't go to bed
very early.
He thinks I do tarot card reading, but I can just sit in my normal clothes with
the sound off.
So there's so many ways of doing this job, but you don't have to be.
Sitted naked or, you know, you can be sitting here like this.
I've got a card going on, fleece, pajama, and crocs.
You know, I don't agree at the moment, but you know, like you can just be like
freshly out the shower with blow dried hair and a dressing gown on, can't you?
The earn money around your children and or around whatever life you have.
And, you know, it can be amazing and it really has completely changed my life
and made things so much easier for me in my life and.
If I don't seem amazing and just be in everyone and have the support from
everyone and the friendships I've made have been unbelievable. So yeah.
Thank you, Sammy.
That's okay.
Anyone else? No pressure. We can move on if you don't.
If anyone else wants to.
I should say actually I was thinking what you're saying that I was thinking,
how's it fit into my life?
Actually, it fits in a little differently now as well because I've got my
couples profile with my boyfriend so that every time we go out together, or
actually, even when we're staying together.
We'll just like be getting ready with the camera and we'll be chatting there,
or we'll just be like in the house chilling, having a couple of drinks, and,
and it'll be on then so it fits into my life that way now as well, which is
quite fun.
I enjoy that at the moment.
Okay, let's move on then shall we say.
So this call is about information and inspiration so we've got a cup two or
three slides with information so we'll just go over some of the, some of the
good stuff.
And then we've got I think three questions, which will open it up to everyone
like we did just then just to hopefully get some inspiration from each other or
to inspire some newbies about different things they can do.
So, so your profile and Georgia, do you want, do you want to be okay to go
through this one.
Yeah, of course.
And okay so with the profile we've spoke about this on a couple of calls and we
do send a lot of information about this, but this is because we believe that it
's really, really important.
To have your profile looking as good as possible because this is the first
point of contact or the first thing that the client has gone to see before they
even see you.
So you wanted to represent you as as good as possible and you know be as I
catch as possible.
And for you to get as many people into the into the chat room.
So there's a couple of different elements to the profile and things you can
work on.
One of the biggest things is that about you section.
So this is basically just a large chunk of text that is shown on your profile.
There's also another smaller chunk of text on top of a little line, like a
summary line, and then the huge about you section.
So in there, this is where you can go into detail and you know about you and
what you like, and what you like to talk about and what you enjoy on cam.
So, and it's good to maybe try and be a little bit more original with this,
because often you see the same type of profiles. I think some groups they just
copy and paste the same thing for everybody and it is a huge amount of text and
get me wrong.
It's a lot on there. So it looks a little bit better. I didn't like you got at
least you've got a lot, but then it's kind of the same as everybody else's so
it's saying, oh, I offer this this and this and then that's it really.
But we think it's good to talk about yourself and what you like, you know, like
normal things, not just, I like to stick dilders up myself or whatever it is.
You know, like, you know, like things that you like and it doesn't even have to
be about you. It can be about your alter ego, of course.
So, yeah, go a little bit more in depth about and stuff that isn't just webcam
based, you know, and you can also create tabs on this section.
So to keep it all clear and in one place.
So, for example, you could have one tab that's about you, and then one tab that
explains more about maybe a certain fetish or pink that you explore on camp
with your clients.
And you can have all different tabs for all different things.
And they're quite easy to make. If you're not sure how to do it, we can help
you with that.
You can also put certain words in bold and, you know, underline certain words
to make certain words or sentences, obviously more I catch on.
You can use emojis.
And there's all kinds you can do to make the text stand out more.
So this is something that we would recommend spend some time on.
We actually have a document and other training calls that go into how to do
your profile in much more detail.
And so be worth taking a look at them as well.
And, you know, if you do and you want to, you want to get your profile on God,
or even if you're not new, it's good to always revamp it and go back through
and, you know, freshen up.
And so yeah, that's the about you section.
Next, we have pictures. So you can have free profile pictures and we think it's
good to use them all why not.
And with your main one, of course, be in the one that's most eye catching.
And with that one, you want to be choosing one where you're taking up a large
chunk of the screen and a large chunk of the photo. Sorry.
So you can see a better on the small screen with with when everybody else is on
there, because basically when you're broadcasting live you're just a small
little photo on a huge screen with all different other in camp camp girls on
there.
So you want your photo to be as stand out as possible, and we can help you pick
the best one that we think that would work out to the photos that you've got.
And then you can also have a free gallery and a private gallery. So in the free
gallery, of course, use pictures that I'm on to revealing as the clients are
going to see these free.
Then if you've got any more revealing pictures or pictures of, you know, stuff
that people are going to buy like for example pictures of your feet and stuff
like that this is like a huge king that people like to, you know, people will
buy pictures.
If it's off your feet and whatnot, and you can put them in your private gallery
, and in your private gallery.
The more pictures you've gotten there the more you can charge, and sometimes
some clients now there's a feature where you can have different private
galleries for different clients, and they can be accessed through a code that
you'll share with your clients so only they will see it.
And so in there you can do more custom made pictures. One of my girls the other
day actually she just, she done so well she just done I think it was like 20
pictures, and she agreed to sell them to them for 500 credits.
And she did for 20 pictures and I was like whoa that amazing so certain clients
will want custom pictures for them and you can actually charge more because the
custom for them you know.
And make your money on the site over then you know not just being on camera.
You can also sell videos as well and that's not written on there but that's
probably the same bracket as the pictures and you can sell videos like an every
single one has a price.
So if you've got 10 20 videos on your profile, your clients could click on
today and if they could buy one or two, somebody else buys one or two and then
before you know it.
The money's just adding up an open up a knock.
Okay, moving on so next we'll discuss the price so
when you first start you'll already have a price per minute set, and this is
going to be the lowest that you're ever going to be on because obviously you're
new the profile is new and basic and we need to get a built up a little bit
more.
And then when we do we can up your price.
So this is something that you can speak to your mentor about if you're not sure
what to charge.
I personally, I like to charge more on the higher end, but not too high.
I don't want to go too high, then more everybody else is charging just because
I also want to be getting calls, you know, so.
So yeah, but this is something that we can help with each individual.
As I'm going. Another important thing about the profile is feedback. So, and
this is.
Basically, and something that the clients can leave you and you can leave them
once you've had a chat with them after the chat's been over a certain amount of
minutes, you get the option to leave your clients feedback and they get the
same.
I always like to leave my clients feedback, even if I didn't actually remember
the call or whatever else, you know, you might have had that many in a day and
you look at the username and think.
Oh, I don't even remember what we spoke about. I would just leave a general
feedback so I'd such a great time with you can't wait to chat with you again or
you know something like that.
But then if I remember the client and the call which I do most of the time, if
it's been a long one, especially, I leave little and I leave like little bits
about the call in the feedback so, for example.
And if it was a domination session and he was a really good and really obedient
, you could write something like, you really impressed your mistress today with
how obedient he was.
And, you know, come like can't wait for next time or I don't know something
like that so they know oh wow she remembers and she thought about me or
whatever else.
So you can do that for your clients, and then hopefully in 10 they will do that
for you, because building up your feedback on the website.
And it is really good and it's really important for making your profile look
more established, making you look more and your profile look more attractive to
other clients.
And this is something that comes in time as well so don't put too much pressure
on yourself in the beginning to have all this feedback because it will just
come in time.
But the more you come in and the more you're leaving your clients feedback the
more likely you are to get left feedback.
So as well as webcam and pick selling pictures and selling videos that are also
other ways to make money on the website.
So there's direct I am SMS and phone calls.
Direct I am is similar to webcam both the only difference is that they can't
see you and you can't see them so it's just a live chat, kind of like MSN back
in the day don't know if you should anyone remembers that.
It's a little bit naughty I suppose. So it's like 13 when I was on MSN.
Yeah, it's just a live chat so I've noticed recently actually a lot of our
members are doing direct I am more than ever.
And I see that people do really well from here, especially if you know that I
haven't got the hair or makeup done or they're in bed and you can't really be
bothered to do all that stuff or they don't have the time to do it.
You can just throw direct I am on and just do video and sorry to text chats. So
, yeah, I think this is a good thing to do like if you're not feeling like you
want to go and come.
Maybe on if you're travelling or I don't know you're on the train or something
like that and you've got time to kill just having it on.
But although I would come on the train if possible if there's nobody around I
would do that because the clients love it love it when you're out and about and
how it's like such a naughty thing. Oh, it's so naughty.
They love it.
What was that.
Honestly, they love it like when I was living in Thailand I'd go on long trips
in the car for hours every so often to renew the visa.
And every time in the car my boyfriend would drive and I would sit in the back
put my cam on. And they would love it like, honestly, I was never busy and then
when I'll be in the back of a car.
I would say to my friends and you should just drive me around and I should just
sit and come because they don't need that room. They're like, Oh, you're out
and about what if people share your own I'm like, Oh, what are they saving.
Anyway, so that's it. It's been all try.
Good idea.
Yeah.
So if you look at the opportunity to I would try that.
Yeah, I'm going back to this so direct I am. When you're on direct I am as well
. We say to charge a little bit less because everybody else says for starters,
every other girl charges a little bit less obviously because they can't see you
.
And so yeah, just make sure to change your price per minute because it doesn't,
you don't have a set one for direct I am at all the same so you just every time
you use that just lower it.
And then remember to hide it back up again when you use come and but we can
help you with that.
SMS. So, with SMS.
I'm not actually sure is it is it did a point five credit so like half a credit
is it so or one of the girls that you go yeah.
So we've got with SMS every time you communicate with your client and you get a
half the credit and that can all add up as well.
So I think it's a good one to use just to keep in contact with your regulars.
So if you ever you know, if you're going online later on in the day you can
text them all back and say you know I'm going online at seven p.m. Let's let's
catch up blah blah blah you know.
So, yeah, I think it's good for obviously making the money but then also good
for the longevity to with your regular clients.
And the same with phone calls so with the phone calls.
How much do you actually get it must be fun like because I've never actually
done phone calls myself so I'm probably not a good one to be speaking about
this.
Does anybody want to break the phone calls lo and are you you're the expert in
phone calls aren't you.
I'll wait to see what's written in the chat about this one.
So, yeah. Hello. Hello. Hi. So I've not got my screen to mind you I might as
well put the screen on as well.
It's just me sitting with a cat.
So yeah, the phone calls obviously set your own price so I think I just have my
point nine five.
The book calls higher like 1.21 because a lot of the time, particularly one guy
I have a books for about minutes and I can't get rid of them for 10 minutes you
know I always charge but I have one so.
Oh, God. Yeah, so did the phone ones are really good actually zoom out and
stuff and I found I get quite a few texts as me because I put it in army
profile as well.
And then I got a text coming and then I'll be texting for a few minutes before
you know you got like 10 to 12 credits which is great you know.
Yeah.
Thank you, Lana. Yeah, you don't really well with phone calls. Yeah.
Sophie, is there anything you'd add to that that phone calls.
I don't think I could add anything. Just they are quite lucrative. I was
talking about today, literally walking around and around the park and trying to
do more walking and whatever.
And then talking to people and same with you, Georgia in the car they love that
you're out and about.
And the like, and one of them was like, well, can you, you know, touch yourself
.
Yeah, my hands like, in my coat and under all my layers and I'm just sitting
here for an instant and obviously I wasn't but it's just, it's quite good to do
anything whilst on the phone.
So it's a good way to make a bit of money whilst you're busy, basically.
Thanks.
Thank you.
And thanks for helping me out with that one girls you know what I would like to
try phone calls one day for.
I don't know. I just feel like I'd probably be like, what do I even say like I
'd probably like, you know, lose like those all train of force but that's
probably why it's good to try it isn't it.
So yeah, you know what I should try it now. So like at least in the future and
they want to talk about as well.
Yeah, I'm like that maybe we should do it together as like a goal sitting thing
. Yeah, maybe we should.
Just do like a week of being on call as well.
Yeah, I'm sure once you've got a few calls, we'll feel fine about it and then
we've got it.
Yeah, it's the same as can, isn't it? When you're so nervous to go on cam and,
and like, then you just like, to me now it's like getting in the bath, you know
, like, or doing the dishwasher.
It's just so normal. So, so I need to get out of my comfort zone and do some
phone calls. Maybe we could do that together actually.
Yeah, let's do it.
Let's do it.
It's really good though, because I think you can just, you know, really top
some money about one of the new girls whose ladies started last week.
And we were just chatting with some young phones. Oh, no, I don't know how to
do it. Set her up. Then she messaged me and I was like, I've had a call, I've
had a call.
And then, we should make a pact as well, like, you go on cab and I'll do fine.
I was going for garden centre, I was talking.
It really had something like, you know what I mean, it's, it is, it is good fun
, you know, it does that also.
It did amazing as well smashing it.
I have a right laugh because I was there doing something and then I jumped with
the phone goes and I'm completely different first, you know, and I go back to
work.
Yeah.
That's nice. Well, thank you for sharing that ladies.
Okay, so finally, and cater to your market.
So, on cam, I feel like the clients on there, a lot of them.
They're exploring fantasies and fetishes and ideas that they would never maybe
explore in your life or with, you know, maybe they've never spoke about this
stuff before and this is their escape.
So, with that being said, if you've got to sit in like kink or niche or
something like that that you do on cam, it's good to really speak about this in
your profile and show that this is your specialty.
Because there's so many different avenues to go down with this.
And if a client sees that you're speaking about his particular fetish, they're
going to, they're going to be like drawn straight to you.
Rather than trying to cater to everybody and say, I do this, I'm going to do
this and this is like, it's might be a little bit overwhelming for your clients
, whereas if you lay out exactly what you offer, you know, what you like what
you enjoy.
That's why this is what I like to do, kind of thing, then you will obviously
attract those clients.
And so yeah, I think that's an important one because, and I know that in the
beginning, maybe if someone use a new, you won't know what you're doing or what
you like yet or what your market's going to be and that's absolutely fine
because it'll all come in time.
But as you start to get more established, it's good to really cater your
profile to reflect what you, you know, what you're offering, rather than it
saying that you like to do all these things and then maybe you don't and, you
know, you're going to get clients coming in who asked for that and
what you often, you know, so, like ever since I named myself goddess Ruby
instead of I used to be Ruby summers, and then I changed as a goddess Ruby
because I wanted it to be more dumb.
Ever since then, like, my clients are like, I'm so much happy with the clients
that come through, because they know it's more of a dumb profile than anything
else so I get a lot less of clients asking me things that I don't like to do.
And so it's better for you as well like you're not going to get the clients
coming in like saying things or asking you things that maybe you don't like or
you're uncomfortable with, or it's just a waste of time because obviously you
're not going to do what they, what that particular client wants so that
that's a waste of time for somebody else, you know, so the more your profile
frecks what you offer and what you like and what you enjoy.
The better, like the better the clients that are going to come through
basically because they're going to vibe with you or your alter ego, whatever
that is, you know.
So yeah, that was just a little bit about the profile but like I said, we do
have a lot more in depth training on this and this is something that is super
important so it's good to spend time.
It's a great profile and your mentor and all of us are always there to help as
well.
Yeah, does anyone want to add anything to some sort of probably left some
things off.
I think like what just an extra thing for catering to your market.
You know, it doesn't have to be a kink or fetish or anything like that it can
be like.
So just start out just thinking about what type of guys are always coming in
your room. So, for example, when I first started, I seem to attract quite a lot
of old men.
So then I would cater to my market I would know that okay who am I writing my
profile to my about section. I'm writing to an older audience here so what do
they want to hear.
I know like, you know, what, you know, maybe a bit more of an intellectual
profile, not use certain words like garage stuff, like, you know, or if, if,
like, for instance, guys are coming in and calling you a mill for all the time,
then catering to your market would be maybe to put milk in your, in your
username.
Or, you know, so like it doesn't necessarily have to be about what you offer,
it can just be about like, what value you're giving off or what, you know, what
, what they want from you like do they want a girl next door who's really
shining a sin.
And you can write your profile that way, or like, you know, whatever, whatever
noticing isn't it's noticing what other people notice about you.
Which I think can be good as well.
Yeah.
Thank you for that Jay, thank you that was that was quite a lot for you to go
through so thank you so much.
Okay, that's a good point for a political point like, notice someone they
notice about you that's yeah that's a great point because
yeah, and I do that in calls, like I noticed if they say a word to me like two
or three times they've repeated this one word, like about me then.
Oh my god, that just becomes me then, like, if they like, they like say that oh
yeah you really you really like you all you've got your businesses and stuff
and then then then they mention it again I'm like okay, this is what this is
what they like in me, or like whatever it is.
You're really you're really curious or you're really like open to this idea and
I'm like okay that's what you want me to be so you're always taking the cues
from them like what they're noticing.
Okay, that's really fun so just a couple more information I'll just go through
these briefly because it's not there's not a load of information on here.
It's a webcam setup so just to make sure that the very basics when you're
actually logging on cam are good and obviously need to have decent webcam and
mic quality.
So you know if people come into your room and they can't really see you or it's
a bit blurry or you know whatever then they're not going to you know they're
just going to click straight off aren't they.
You know, you've got HD cams and you know light in an airy space and so just
making sure that your cam quality is okay.
And that your lighting is okay as well like lovely Kelly in the picture there
and it's got a ring light and lots of different lights and stuff.
You can use ring lights so making sure you've got decent light every night if
possible, you can get them for like 12 quid or something and home bargains I
think.
And all just propping up a lamp behind your thing I think I did that for quite
a while when I first started behind the laptop.
The space around you so just being mindful of the space around you that it's
quite clear that it's not too cluttered or nothing's like, you know, drawing
attention away or, you know, that it, that it kind of maybe goes for your
persona I guess that's on there as well does the space your persona but yeah
the things around you if they reflect
who you are on can like or just got a beautiful camera room now, then it helps
doesn't it just draws you in and it's really inviting and it adds to adds to
the whole experience.
And comfort obviously comfort's important because you're going to be sitting
there for a long periods of time.
And so yeah, making sure that you're comfortable.
And even that you take like breaks when necessary when needed and, you know,
part of being comfortable as well for me is like having TV on in the background
or music or something so that I'm not just sat there.
And so yeah making yourself comfortable I think it's important because then you
're just in the right space, you're not getting annoyed, you know, or
uncomfortable.
And that comes across on camera isn't it.
And you can change it up so, like you were saying, you can do it like out and
about in the car, the train, you know, wherever you want to really.
Or, you know, in different places in your house or whatever just changing up I
know a few girls that come from the bath.
It's just changing it up and seeing what works and what works for you as well.
And, and then, you know, we often talk about this one as well and it's having a
good camera team.
So, you know, like any job, you know, it's good to have a routine.
And, you know, habits, good habits, getting to good habits because this is a
business at the end of the day and we're here to, you know, we want to make
money.
We also want to have fun but we want to make money and we want to feel good
about it.
So it's really good to get into a good camera team if you can.
So these are five sort of steps that I think about when I'm like going to go on
cam.
And of course there's times when you just like flick it on, because you've just
got a spare hour or whatever so, you know, you don't always have to go through
like all these steps but I think if I know I'm going to be on for a few hours.
And I like to just do these things do these little rituals and getting to the
right energy and stuff, if I'm going to be going on.
So first I think about my energy so I'll make sure that I'm feeling okay I'm
not too tired, you know, it's best to skip it if I'm feeling really crappy.
And that I've got good energy might put some music on like do my hair make up
get myself in the zone.
Then I'll think about my space so like I said on the previous slide, you know
the lighting where I'm going to go if I'm comfortable grab a cup of tea like
and think about my space and make sure that's set up.
And then I'll think about my looks like what I'm going to wear.
And then of course it doesn't have to be like, you know you don't have to spend
an hour getting ready to go on you can just go on this in the morning when you
wake up you can go on anytime.
However you are, but depending on your persona and your niche you might want to
look a certain way when you go online.
And then, I'm sure not everybody does this but I like to say this I think it's
a good way to start is to think of the story so like what story are you going
on with today.
So I always like I'll think about how I'm feeling that day so maybe I'll be
feeling like done that day. So I'll change my strap line my tagline my profile
to see something quite dummy.
Or I'll be wearing a certain thing so I'll change it and say that, but I'll
always have a story so I'll be like what mood am I in, what do I actually want
to talk about or do.
And then I'll change my tagline and I'll think of something a story I think of
something that I can say that goes with the way I'm feeling.
So like, I might say to the people that come in and they always say how you
like I am great. I just have stressful day at work so I feel like taking out on
someone or you know whatever whatever it is I'll think of a little bit of a
story or a little bit of something to say.
It goes along with that so that you're not always just waiting for the client
to give you something you've got something to give of your own straight up the
bat you're already giving them something and you're already like intriguing
them and drawing them.
And that's part of my routine to think about the story. What's my story today
or just a little tip bit of information. I've got some new lingerie like you
like it or whatever I'm going to wear it for this or that.
That's the story. And then the last bit is to treat it like a business. So to
think, have I did so I'm going to be on the front page.
Am I going to do free chat to get myself a bit noticed. Have I replied to my
messages.
You know, going through all the steps to make sure that your profiles going to
be seen as much as possible.
And what my goals as well like what's my goal for the day. How's my goal for
the week going to treat it like a business is that last step to me just get me
like right. Yeah, I'm going on now ready.
Does anyone else want to.
Does anyone else got anything that they do for their camera team or any
anything they'd add to that.
There's different things that probably comes on to the story by usually have
like a hospital award or a police station, where it's kind like a military one.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, there's a.
And we did a call on like fantasy writing and which is good to get some
inspiration for like stories and stuff like that.
I think it's just good to go on with a little tip that a little something to
offer a little something to say, even if it's that small.
It's just easy way to start conversation and then it brings out other things as
well.
Hi.
Hello.
Can you hear me.
Yes.
Sorry I'm just doing like bedtime as well at the same time.
So I also always make sure that I think you've already said this already is a
well but being comfortable and being.
You know, making sure that you feel comfortable and I think that's quite
important to look to know that yourself that you look sexy or look comfortable
or feel okay with what you're wearing or how you look.
Because I think it massively shows on can doesn't it if you if you feel
uncomfortable and you feel that you don't look good or whatever that that can
be seen straight away so as long as you feel comfortable and feel happy and
settled and.
You know, going up the best mindset that you could possibly can before you can.
I think he's always good.
Yeah, definitely says me running around the house trying to put kids to bed
because they were going to sleep multitasking.
I'm going to meet myself now.
Sorry girls.
Thank you for that family bless you.
No worries.
Okay, so, next I think we just got some questions that we thought we could, you
know, we could all sort of chip in in, you know, inspire each other hopefully
with with answer to some questions that we often get asked.
So we've, we've said that there's like, you know, so many ways that you can
count so many different things you can do, maybe this will hopefully give us a
bit of an insight into some of what those things might be.
So, what is your current webcam persona and what are your top tips for that
niche.
Does anybody want what to start off does anybody.
My combination.
Yeah. Okay.
I just, I specialise in, um, domination on your.
And what, what would you say your, your tips and things are for that me.
It's really weird. And I'm just the way I speak.
And sometimes, I mean, I am realised I would never even speak like it, but some
of them, it's so vile.
And they love it. They love me.
Sometimes it can make us feel a bit powerful as well, doesn't it? Like,
sometimes I actually just really enjoy it. I just, I get playful with it and
curious with it. And I just kind of roll with it.
That's how I'd be normally in my, in my day, say life, but I actually super
enjoy being like that.
Yeah, it takes a while, I think, to like, to find that in yourself, but now I'm
like, Oh, love it.
And you can actually have some lovely relationships with guys who are so, like,
I find I have some, like, really, really lovely conversations with them and
they like, they're so appreciative of your time and your direction and stuff.
And so I was, I was explaining to my mum the other day about how you actually
form after, you know, what I've been doing in only two years.
It's weird, but you form like a kind of friendship with your regulars, like you
trust them, they trust you, like, I don't know, like I miss them sometimes if I
don't speak to them for a few days.
And it's this weird kind of relationship where you don't actually meet someone,
but you actually do end up having what I do, like, a bit of a bond with someone
, and like, you kind of like care about them as well a little bit.
You know what I mean, like, yeah, I don't know, it's weird to explain it, but
you do feel like, Oh, are they okay? They've been on, they've been on for a few
days.
And they're all right. I had their wife's all right, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Yeah, I feel the same, I totally feel like that I have friends that I've come
with for five years and they're great and I love speaking to them, and I love
it when I see their names pop up and I'm like, Oh, hi.
Yeah, it's nice. It's this weird kind of friendship you didn't realise was even
available in, well, I didn't realise could ever be available in my life. And I
do kind of have these like connections with people and I feel like, I don't
know, like, I look forward to speaking to some of them sometimes, you know,
like they're okay and
you know, they give me the lifestyle that I can live so I'm appreciative of
them.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, and it's nice for them to build it, you know, they're helping
you as well in some way.
Yeah, so, it's a weird thing to explain, I think, like trying to explain it in
words, but yeah, I think it's, you do kind of get to that point where you, you
do make a connection with some of them, not all of them, but some, you know,
like they might be the one or two that after a year or so you make a little
connection with them.
And they become, you know, a part of your life, really. Yeah, yeah. And I think
like what's nice about web cameras that well personally for me, your profile
and your niche can change over time.
So it can change with you. Like, when I first went on my, I guess my thing was
that because I don't know anything like I didn't know what I was doing.
So I was just like, I'll just, I'll just go on and see what happens, I'll just
flirt and see what happens and I guess the guys loved that I was new, and they
do don't let they love any new day so kind of played on that.
And, and I started to start talking to them honestly and I'll tell them how it
just come out of a really long relationship, and I was just wanting to explore
more things.
And then I realised that they absolutely fed on that they loved it they just
thought I was really innocent and stuff so I think when you're doing like girl
next door type of thing.
And a good tip for that is just to be, you don't need all the you don't have to
have the answers, you don't have to know what things are it's actually good
thing if you don't know what they're talking about because then they can
explain it so you're at length and you can earn money by doing that.
So you can cash in on being a new day.
And then, as time went on I got, I quite enjoyed like sub fantasies and stuff
so I got really into that so that that was like my niche for a little bit.
And then now.
I'm switch, I'm a switch so it says switch on my profile mostly do dumb stuff
but and yeah you pray for like really grow with you can't it can really change
over time.
And yeah I think that's what's nice about it you're not stuck to one knee she
can do different things.
Yeah, what would you say if you got any like top tips do you feel like
domination.
Yes, so, so like you said with the niches changing. I, my main one would be
domination but then also, I got just a lot of kind like a lot of guys in that
just him.
That just want to see like my body or whatever else so then I just do like the
girlfriend experience slash T's like that's another thing that I seem to do a
lot so I just, you know, show them a little bit and put it put it back down and
top back down and show them like this
and that.
So then them chats as well they can be dragged on for quite some time and I'm
literally just teasing them showing them different parts of my body and having
a little bit of a naughty chat.
So that's feels good for me as well. So I do both and what the domination I
enjoy that more that's in that's something I really like so with that my top
tips.
I would say just be like slow and don't feel like you have to like come up with
all kinds and like, you know, don't overthink it just take your time.
You're in control like this is your, this is how you wanted to go this chat and
yeah I think I used to try and think like oh what can I make them do next and
they need to be doing this and this this and like trying, you know, come up
with all these ideas
and really they just want to be like held and in your attention, you know what
I mean so that's another thing as well with the domination like just really
hold them in your like in this moment and put your attention on to them, like
always back out on to them.
Rather than like, you know, like always reflected back on to them and like,
yeah, I don't know if I'm making much sense here.
It's like bouncing off each other, go with a flow. Yeah, exactly.
If you want to put your attention out like if you are being more submissive it
's more like.
Like you asked like they've maybe asking you questions or they're getting to
know more about you and pulling things out of you but it's when you're doing
domination it's more like you're putting your attention out on to them.
And top tips for domination as well, I would say don't assume that everyone,
everyone like sub is into the same stuff or likes it as harsh as the others
because there are some guys who are into domination and maybe they've only just
started it or maybe they've
done it for a long time but still, they're very like they like the more tame
side of it. But then there's others who really want to go all out and like you
know sometimes they'll even shock me with some of the things they they've said
or they want
or whatever else. So just get to know each clients specifically and not it's
not just like one, one shoe fits all kind of thing.
And also as well like asking questions because this is something that I didn't
think was really even allowed in the domination world in the beginning.
But it is like we should like before, especially before you start the session
properly, ask like questions like what do you, what like how would a perfect
in Dom session look like to you.
This is a question I like to ask because then they will tell me and then I can
deliver that to them like deliver it like as good as possible you know.
I can really ask questions and not just with Domination but I suppose if
anything like you're doing, get to know what the client wants.
And then if you feel good about delivering that to them, then perfect
because then you can literally give them exactly what they want.
And that's what we want really because we want to be pleasing the clients
because we want to retain customers you know what I mean.
It would be my top tips for that. But yeah, anybody else got anything to add
about Domination or anything in general.
Yeah, but the domination.
I know the domination I've got is different on a different place, but it's
similar thing.
When I go to Domination, I've got myself and always for the first 10 minutes
for the bottom.
And it'll be the same as webcam. I've always sat down with them and got to find
out who they were, what they wanted and what the boundaries were.
I mean, we found that was very important in Domination because it's the other
step them boundaries that can send them off, even on time I got it.
And if you have a step them boundaries, even on webcam, you'll soon click off,
they'll go.
So I always like to find out at the beginning.
Now just from up in the chat, it's like, so I feel like you have how far do you
like to go with this.
And then I get to find out through 12 concerned, just normal, just normally 12
concerned.
And then they'll tell me everything's what they want within the first 5 to 10
minutes.
It's like a table go for that. And then I start Domination. I don't actually
start it straight away.
Mm hmm.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
Really good.
Really good tips there. And I think like you were saying, you know, about this
attention being outwards to, I think that's really good.
Anyway, like I think that's it. Like you said, that's especially like, you know
, what you want to do when you're when you're done.
But I think anyway, remember we're in control here. We're, we're, you know,
this is our space.
So who is this person coming into our space? Like, I always see that person as
my, the spotlight is on them.
So that spotlight that's on them helps me to analyze what they're saying, like,
okay, how can I make the best out of this session?
Because I, because I'm hearing everything they're saying, I can drag it out of
them what they want because they'll tell you, they always tell you what they
want.
If you just like can engage them in conversation, whatever type of coming you
're doing, they will always tell you what they want.
So listening, they're having the spotlight on them and all the attention on
them.
And you can really just sit back and relax and let them listen to them and let
them open up to you.
And also that kind of works for when guys are not so nice, you know, when you
get the odd one who you're not vibing with, you know, just the attention still
on them.
They're, they're the ones that are paying to be in this space. So like, you
know, if they say something to you that you don't quite like just reflecting it
back and putting that, putting that attention back onto them.
You know, I don't know if that's making sense.
It is, it's making much time.
Hey, Elle, I've got a question for you.
Yeah, sure.
You just said that you're a switch and I'm a switch as well.
But I honestly have a hard time.
Like, my main thing is usually, or right now I'm still like really on OnlyFans
and on social media and stuff so I'm just really new to coming.
But my issue is really that I have a bit of an awkward thing where I have a
hard time being both, if that makes sense. I feel like everyone needs me to
pick just one.
But I like both and I have different moods. So how do you deal with that?
Yeah, thank you. That's a really good question and something that I have like
pondered over a lot and sometimes found hard as well.
And I think like, firstly, my profile. So my first bit of my profile is just
about me. It's not about sub or DOM or anything. It's just about me.
And then I will go into, I'll have like a tab for my DOM and then a tab for
more sub stuff.
And I guess more of the emphasis for me is on the DOM because that's, I know
that I could DOM with pretty much anybody, but I don't think I can't sub with
it.
You know, anybody. So the emphasis for me is more on that.
And I think I personally don't do free chat because firstly, it drains my
energy. I'd much rather spend money on bidding to be on the front page and just
watch TV in the tingles.
But, but secondly, because that's where I find it most hard, like, because
there's just so much coming at you and you can't, you know, you can't be all
those personas at this point.
You're all those personas at the same time.
So yeah, free free. I found it really difficult in there. So I don't really do
free.
But it can be, you know, I found sometimes it can be like, you just have to
work with what you've got, basically, don't you know, if you've got a couple of
guys in group, it can be quite fun.
And so, especially the longer that you're on cam and the more regular you are,
the more regulars you'll have.
And so each of my regulars, even if, you know, say, one's a DOM and one's a sub
, they might come into my room at the same time, but because I've got such a
good relationship with both of them.
And both of them think that like, they're the special one that I love to come
with because all my regulars think that, you know, one of them will be think he
's the one who's in on it while I'm talking to this other guy in a certain way.
And I think that about the other, that makes sense.
So I think like the more you're online, it's just building good relationships
with people so that even if they see you doing something different, it's kind
of like you're in on it with them, you know.
And also, you can't please everyone all the time as well, like, you know, being
a switch is kind of like, you know, we're kind of looking at that.
But yeah, we can't do that. And, you know, even if we could, we don't want to
sometimes and that's okay.
And so picking one out and going for that one I think sometimes is good.
With a switch, you could do a lead-up story, but the switch, the hands of the
switch, I doubt this quite a few times, I'll get someone who wants me to be
dumb.
And halfway through the switch is over. I've got a mindset for it.
So using it to try and beat the dom, the dom which is me. So there's a practice
artwork on the sub version.
And then halfway through, so certainly any cycle competition, there's one the
domination.
Yeah, I love that.
I really enjoyed that.
It's like a storyline with it. And I talk to the prayer and I'm dominating them
for the first half.
And then all of a sudden they're just switching. It's like, I've also powered
the domination.
And that is the biggest riff on the switch side of things.
But I can switch my mind pretty good. I can go from domination to sub to sub to
dom.
It's really easy for me in that way.
Yeah, I think like just every relationship you have on cam is unique, isn't it?
So we can put it under these like headings of, okay, I'm your dom and you're
myself now.
But every relationship is unique. So you don't bully ever know where it's going
to go with someone or you shouldn't,
you know, because you should always be open to their cues and just letting it
flow together.
But yeah, that was a really good question because it can be hard to hold those
two things.
But I think coming from where you feel that day as well is important.
Like when I say about the camera to you, like, I think about how I feel first
of all.
And if I don't feel, you know, if I feel dom, then I'll put on some latex and
put in my strap line, something domy.
And then you tend to get more of those calls or vice versa. So that's a good
thing to do as well.
Thank you for answering.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Okay.
Let's move on to the next one, shall we? Can't remember this one or two left.
Let's have a look.
Okay.
Lovely picture of Jay.
How do you grow your business and get more clients in?
Well, does anybody want to go first in this?
Shall I say something?
Yeah, go ahead, Sami.
Okay, so for me, I would say being consistent is so important to grow your
business.
Some days, even now I will still have days where I look on for two hours.
And I will still pay to be on the front page and I might not always get any
calls.
I might get one or two.
I might only earn nine credits.
Do not be disheartened.
It happens to all of us, even with experience and feedback and really great
profiles.
You're always going to have maybe one day a week that's quiet.
But if you keep at it, you'll have four days a week that are super busy.
That will make up for that one day a week that's really quiet.
I know it's really hard to be disheartened sometimes when you're, you know, you
're starting out or any time you can have three days in a row that are super
quiet.
Like, oh, and you can easily feel a little bit disheartened by it or a little
bit like, oh, why is this happening or whatever.
But stick to it, be consistent, log on, because the day after or the day after
that, you could earn like 400 credits in three hours or whatever.
You know, like the good always overcomes the quiet days.
I think if you're consistent, it's just that sometimes you have to log in.
Like you say, like, watch, have the TV on whatever, like, so it's, you don't
feel like it's sitting staring at your laptop.
Because you will have the quiet days, but the, the busy day sort of make up for
the quiet ones as well.
That's what I always think like, when I have a busy day, I make sure that I put
a little bit of that money away for the quiet days.
And that's how I've kind of kept it like a steady income rather than, I mean,
as much as it's great when you have a really busy day to like be like,
oh, we're going to go shopping tomorrow.
Like we all do.
I always like trying now over like a five day week or five times looking in per
week.
If I have a busy day, I'll put like a little bit of that away, like a bird or a
half of it to make up for the quiet day.
And I just feel like that's really worked for me to make it like a steady
income.
Because calm can be quite an up and down income if you don't treat it like that
.
And if you're someone who's got bills to pay and stuff like that, it's nice to,
to, to make it a steady income.
Does that make sense?
Yeah.
And to grow it.
Yeah, just, I, I just think consistency.
I always, I, I am trying to put myself at the top of the page.
So I will pay for an hour, like three credits or four credits to, to put myself
up at the top.
And then as soon as you start getting one or two privates, I feel like then
they start rolling in.
Because then you're constantly at the front of the page on the top of the page,
sorry, the top.
Yeah.
Um, yeah.
I don't know what else, but yeah, I'd say consistency.
And try and not feet towards position now and again, even if it's just like
once every couple of days.
And I tend to, on the phones, I tend to, especially towards the end of the
month, a day.
But usually on Fridays, there's days and Fridays after one o'clock, a look to
position.
No, it's great on the phones, because it's only like 0.30 credit, you know, it
's not even half a credit.
You'd be on the front page and, you know, available third down.
And I find that's where I put my new people on.
And then I do this periodically and I've got about five or six regulars doing
that for a set myself a limit.
I have to teach it to the day.
Um, it's about four credits on the phones, which is, it's worked out. Okay. But
I just found you thinking, well, I haven't looked at the credit. It's in all.
It's a bit time. I'll just go for like the point three, three, oh, and, you
know, for an hour or two. And that tends to get you there.
And you tend to put a couple of new people on that. That's what I found anyway.
And you're not spending that on awful lot, you know, because I'm on the phone.
It's obviously not in as much, but it has worked for me anyway.
Thank you, Lana. That's really good advice. Thank you.
Um, I, I position every time I go on, every time I wouldn't, I wouldn't really
go on cam without positioning. I always do.
Um, but I don't really do free chat. See some people do free chat and they
really enjoy that and hook their clients in from there.
Um, for me, I know it's not, it's different for everyone, but for me, I, I go
for quality over quantity.
So I probably see less people, but they become regulars, like a chat to the
same people a lot.
So I just really try and hone in on them, build a really good relationship with
them, like, notice things about them, remember them, write down a little
notebook, the ones that you've spoken to for a long time so that I can, because
you do forget them, obviously.
Um, and yeah, I just really concentrate on, you know, getting the good ones,
hooking them in and keeping them, if I can, messaging them when I'm online,
getting them to hot list me.
Um, and anything, anything you'd add to Jina about growing your business and
getting clients in?
Um, yeah, what you've said, I've all been amazing, like consistency is a big
one for sure, because I noticed if I've not been on a while, then I'm not so
busy when I first go back on, but then once I've been on a few times, I noticed
the same people coming back so you can pick up new
regulars really fast, and just by going on in the same time slots. I remember
there was one time I'd go on the same, like the weekends, for example, around
the same time, and I was just getting the same people.
I was like, this is just deja vu from last weekend and last weekend and last
weekend, but I didn't mind that because it was making me money still, you know.
Um, so yeah, so consistency is a big one, just to reiterate that. Um, but also
as well, like, like how to grow the business, how to grow your business, sorry,
just always treating it like a business and putting your best self forward and
your best, like, energy forward, you know what I mean, like, this is for you.
You're growing your business, you're, this is all your thing, you know. Um, so
yeah, just given like 110% effort and energy because it's all feeding back into
you and building up your business, you know.
Like, somebody like me, he's going to be getting on cam really I mean I did do
a couple, but it was over a year ago, and getting on camp for the first time.
And so would you say sort of penciling like all I'm going to do like Thursday
and Friday night, and I'm looking to aim to get like under credit to something
just to give yourself a little go because I don't know what could end or how
long would need to be on to earn it.
So just penciling say two or three nights, three nights say with them, you know
, pick up a figure that's quite doable in some ways, but a little bit stretch to
what you think you know because that to me would be double for what I'm getting
on the phones, wouldn't it, you know, it means
it's just how to plan it out for myself really, you know.
Yeah, so definitely you'll notice that you'll make money and you probably
noticed actually that you'll make it faster on cam just because obviously it's
more pay a minute and maybe you could keep the clients in longer.
But to be honest, I'm not even sure how long like the phone calls even go for
like how long would you speak on the phone for usually what would be like a
normal conversation.
Because you can get, you know, you get some of them just don't like, you know,
two minutes, you know, like two credits, and then I've got a guy just put this
regular guy and I had a bit of quiet quiet days and then I just put my profile
on the point 40 of the credit,
and put this guy up a graduate prep, I'm only was only renewed as credits three
, four times he was on for like an hour and 10 minutes.
The average I think it was about five, six minutes so it's not a lot so you
know, you need quite a few calls and I've got a little niche now with a couple
of them who were abroad long enough straightly won't gain speed, and they
actually send me a little
bit of a clip, I've suggested we watch a little video together so we do that on
the phone that's quite good because I don't really have to say an awful lot.
Like you got into this and it's going well for you know, I have a real, you
know, sometimes like you normal life you get the stress is not that sometimes I
just really come off and I'm laughing my head off you know it's so, so fun so
yeah.
Never a dull day with this job.
You've got a lovely energy law now. Yeah, really.
I know ones that they don't want to get off the phones here and I would do the
same.
But yeah so like you said as well we've got a more clients in I always position
as well and ever usually do free chat.
Just because my experience with free chat isn't great but I know that some of
our girls do it and love it and it, the end of getting but guys into private
and making so much which is amazing.
But for me, it just doesn't seem to work it seems like they just the clients
are just freeloaders in there a lot of the time.
But so I I would say it's a position for the front page. But if you're new and
you don't have credits then try and free chat could be great as well because it
can get you to the front page without having to pay.
And then hopefully you can get them into pay chats.
But another thing you can actually do to get more clients in and we've spoke
about this before but I'll just mention it again for anyone who wasn't here.
Email them back old regulars or just just you know email and back anyone who's
emailed you.
So maybe you've logged on and you've got some emails in your inbox that you've
not attended to, you can send them all the email straight away to say oh I'm
back online now like I've been off for a couple of days or whatever it was.
So back now, are you are you around be nice to catch up blah blah blah or even
just if you don't have any emails or as well as as well as appliance the ones
you've got.
Maybe just look through your email list and see if there's any names near that
you've recognised that I've regular clients and then just send them another one
like send another reply.
So just like a fresh email kinds of thing and just tell them that you're back
online and see how they've been you know see if they're about for a chat.
I mean that's what's working because I went through your first week in January
or hi Happy New Year, hope you will be great chat soon and I must go about 20
replies.
And then I found out from that direct chat log that I found by accident just to
see, you can actually email or you call us from there.
I just that was free. I emailed about 50 and I got a few replies as well so
that was quite good so yeah.
Yeah you may as well we may as well use as much as we can like use to utilize
exactly and it's free to do it.
And you can just do it while you're waiting for calls you know so you're sat
waiting for calls anyway so go into emails and email everyone back.
I was just copy a little little no some just copy and paste it quick and on and
copy.
Yeah.
I think I think content as well like you know your your you grow as much as you
know you need you put time and attention into it and it grows as an end part of
that time and attention is like editing your profile changing your tagline.
Putting more and more pictures on there like the more pictures the better like
different types of pictures coming to shoot so that you can get good content as
well so that you can put more content on there.
And like buying yourself nice lingerie I think that's a good way to get exactly
.
Definitely that's the thing like we've got to reinvest back into the business
so this is your business so for example, maybe you'll start off and you won't
have a ring light or you won't have.
You know all of these different lingeries or props or this other than as you're
going on and you're making money.
Put some of like take out the same percentage of that money to reinvest back
into this business and back into yourself you know.
So yeah so buy the nice underwear that makes you feel sexy to give you that
extra bit of boost and confidence because although the clients might not notice
that it's brand new ones away.
You like your energy will be different and that will what is what will make you
more money you know.
So yeah like invest back into yourself for sure that's like that's a big one
and I have always done that and I always will like for example, this come room
that I've like set up in Australia.
I don't even know how long I'm going to be in this house for but I think while
I'm here and the camera will pay for itself and it already has paid for itself
you know, and then it will continue to make me more.
So obviously, like that's me like invest and back in by just spending up this
money but then it already came back to me and so yeah, don't be afraid to
invest in yourself and in this business too.
And obviously like you know depending on how far you want to go with it but
like you can link it with Twitter can't you.
Yeah, business card and give them to people if you really want to do like you
know you can give anyone your your link or whatever so you know depending on
how discrete you want to be you can always be growing it that way as well.
Yeah, definitely I think some of our members already have, well I know I know
they definitely do have Twitter's and Instagrams and like under their come name
or like you know, a different name.
And some of them do full picture, some of them just show part of the body or
whatever else so then even even the Instagram and Twitter is quite discreet and
anonymous as well.
And they're not another way to get clients in as see the thing is with other
work it's a really good thing about it.
Even if you don't have obviously the Twitter and Instagram and whatnot you can
still get loads of clients in because they're already there waiting to come the
girls that are available.
And then, if you want to and if you feel to then why not try and bring clients
in from other other places so bring them in from social media, or like well
said maybe you can have a card to give out.
Like to be honest I should probably do that now because I've never done that
before but I'm probably going to do that because I mean people don't tell them
about it anyway and show them my link on the on the phone.
So I know have a card of like a maybe a QR code that takes some straight to it
you know, yeah, yeah.
On my Twitter account when I go on to camp it notifies all my fans on Twitter
because it'll send a link and that I'm online.
Yeah, so I actually get some of my fans off Twitter going to webcam just to
talk to me because I never paid for a mum's Twitter.
I don't think any of them, but they're coming to webcam and talk to me.
When you do that is obviously probably set up a separate email account, won't
you?
Well yeah, no I need to find that.
Yeah, it's linked to a AdultWork when you go into your details and they don't
work you can click the social media link it.
So when and then when you go on to webcam, you click I click the button for
Twitter and it notifies that all my fans on Twitter that I'm not.
And it sends the link to Twitter. So when they click on that link, it sends and
directs my webcam.
Oh clever.
Yeah, I like that.
I got a few thousand pounds.
Yeah.
A lot.
On Twitter.
Wow.
Yeah.
Thank you Anastasia.
Yeah, that's really good.
That'll be great one especially if you've got, you know, a bit of a following
on Twitter.
That's amazing.
Yeah.
Yeah, it is.
It's not that funny.
I think we've got one question left, which is one that people always ask.
So we thought that we put it on here.
And so how do you keep your boundaries and still make money.
People ask this question, ask me this question a lot.
So I think that.
Let's ask the question earlier.
Yeah, when I was saying that, you know, you don't have to please every client.
So like come from that place to start with.
Because.
Yeah, we don't have to please every client.
And the clients that come straight into your chat and are like, get naked.
Or whatever, our clients that are not going to stay anyway, because they just
want a quick flash.
So, and you're going to make nothing.
So picking your clients and being able to say no, being okay with saying no.
Or just just canceling the call.
Like sometimes if the energy is not right, I'll just kick someone out.
I won't even tell them why.
And so it's, you know, you can, you can always do that, can't you? And
sometimes, you know, getting rid of one person makes way for another person,
you know, a person who's going to chat to you and vibe with you.
And I think like maybe being clear on what your own boundaries are first, like
writing them down and actually thinking about what they are.
And, and maybe appreciating that they might change different days, they might
change with different clients, like depending on how you feel.
So really getting to know yourself and always like checking in with yourself
while you're on camp.
And what else anything.
Do you did you want to say something to do other.
Yeah, so like I said before about kicking off the clients if they're just
giving off bad energy.
Honestly, like don't be afraid to let clients go that are not like good for you
.
This is something that like in the beginning, I used to think that I have to
try and keep every client in the room and please them all and which is never
going to be possible anyway.
So trust me, there is more than enough clients to go around. And, and yeah, if
it's just not feeling good to you then, of course, just let them go for
somebody else to come in.
And I did have somewhere I was going to expand on this point and now it's just
like that we had as I started talking we are going to go with this. Let me just
think for the moment.
Oh, I have to make this and I've completely forgot. It'll come back to me.
Yeah, I think that like we, we sometimes like, especially new people are
working from the assumption that there's one type of webcam girl and that there
's one time I've come in.
And that like you have to please everyone all the time, but it's not the case,
like you can make money, but you don't need to take clothes off to make money.
And you know you don't need to talk about certain things even.
And also you can talk about certain things. It doesn't mean that you have to do
them. So you know you can have boundaries like, you know, I'll talk about all
sorts of things that would never dream doing, but it's, it's fantasy and, and
it's okay, you know, so, I think,
if you have an image in your head of what you think you should be doing, scrap
that image and start from what, where you are right now, like what you, what
feels okay and just like take the signals from your body about what feels
okay, get to know your body a bit, if you get like a feeling and not in your
stomach, whatever is going on, listen to it.
And practice during that the more you practice listening to yourself, the
easier it'll be.
You know, it goes on doesn't it, and you get confidence and you're so many
changes as well, doesn't it, you know, and you become all these different
people. So it just takes time doesn't it in building things up and then you, I
've noticed that suddenly change
I mean, some of the things I do and talk and laugh, you know, I wouldn't have
thought when I started and it just, you just evolved and you really, you know,
yeah.
So, I got my boundaries from experience, so I know where they can go and where
they can't, and it's a step off the line. I just, it's gone. I don't mess about
with them.
Yeah.
Those are the warning, those are the warning not to go there, and some of them,
they just blatantly just ignore you, don't they, some of them. And so, they're
pushing a lot enough to solve that line and I just kick them out and the block.
Yeah, I think for me, my boundaries are based on my feelings. So my boundary is
, if I don't feel good about this, then I'm not doing it. So it's like, my
boundary is not about what I'm going to do.
It's more about how I feel. So I could be doing something that I never thought
I would do that day, but if I feel good, it's fine.
Or I could be doing, I could not want to talk about something that talk about
all the time, just because the energy is wrong and I don't like it.
Yeah, it's, it's also the energy you get back off the person as well, isn't it?
Because you got two people, three people could ring and say the same thing, but
you just get a different vibe of people.
The way, you know, the, you know, the altitude and the way the same things, it
's, it's bizarre. And sometimes you say, Oh, I can't be doing with it. So, you
know, just sort of, just the way people say things, I think. So, yeah, you've
got to tune in, haven't you?
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
Everyone, isn't that this clients for everyone? Like, if that thing that you're
interested in, that you is a bit weird, like there'll be someone that's also
like that, you know, whatever it is.
I had a guy, he was literally the webcam mate, and he was calling me a man.
And he was like, this is definitely a man. And I literally used to be able to
put it off. And it was so intrigued. And I was like, I just got this. I'm
usually gone to God, but he was like moaning about being a man.
And I was like, but you're paying to talk to me. So you must, I'm seeing it.
Yeah.
I've got about four, four credits out of him before he came in. And it was me.
Well, at the end.
Anybody else? Is anyone else have anything to add on that?
I remembered what I was going to say now, actually.
But I was going to say was like, also, by keeping to the boundaries, like,
remembering that what you offer people do want. Like, I used to think, because
I'm not doing this or because I'm not showing everything and, you know, using
toys and myself because I used to think that's what
webcam was, but before I started, you know, all that time ago, I used to think
that's the only way you could make money. And because I wasn't doing that.
I, for the first few years, I really limited my potential because of my own,
like, thoughts on it in my own mindset, you know, and it's only, it took time
for me to realise that you can make money and doing anything.
And, and everything, and it doesn't need to be just what you think is expected
or whatever else. So, remember that as well when you're thinking about your
boundaries.
Don't feel like you have to go that big favour because you feel like that's the
only way to make money. It's definitely not.
But yeah, that's all that was going to add to that.
Yeah, I did the hard way because I did try some things that I thought, oh, I
don't want to do that again, you know.
But then also, like well said, like one of my main things like, well, my main
thing now is definitely how I feel like, like you said, say it in clients,
maybe some clients, I like to do all kinds and go, you know, do all of this,
all this stuff with.
But other ones, they won't even get a smile out of me because they're just
being so rude and I'm just like, no, like you're not going to get anything out
to me, you know.
So, like, just always judging it on the energy you're getting, how you're
feeling, and, and not being afraid to say no as well.
Yeah, yeah.
I know you like using the group if you ever feel like you want to vent about
something or like you're not, you're not sure like just popping a message in
the group because there's like amazing women in there that are just there at
the click of a button on the always.
Yeah, brilliant group, isn't it?
Okay, ladies, well, and it's half nine now so we're pretty much coming to the
end of the course, but just, I know it's gone so quickly.
But does anyone have any questions or, you know, anything they'd like to add
any questions.
Anybody? No, no questions, we'll normally have a few at the end of the call.
It's a good one and we covered everything.
Okay, I would like to say thank you actually because I've been struggling with
come and I feel a bit inspired against it as nice.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah, what's a good tip.
Oh, thank you ladies. Thank you.
And thanks everyone who's chipped in and contributed and ask questions and
given their advice and stuff that's what we love we all want to learn from each
other.
Yeah, so it's amazing so our next call.
I think it's the mental health cause isn't it next week.
That's trauma and healing next.
I think we'll be in the notice board.
Okay, yeah, and then we're going to have the body confidence.
Oh, actually.
Oh, yeah, that's after that, I think, isn't it? Yeah, then we'll have the body
body confidence one comment up as well.
The idea is about the Liverpool meeting what sort of time dates at all yet at
all.
Is it just all up in the area.
That's a question, isn't it?
We will let you know over the next day.
It's a bit tricky because Easter's in April, isn't it this year as well.
It's sort of like the second week in April, isn't it Easter.
So only reason I'm asking myself to stay at the end as well.
I bless you.
We will post it in the notice board.
Over the weekend.
So, yeah, but yeah, look forward to announcing that and look forward to meeting
some more lovely ladies as well.
And of course, just, well, just go to the notice board group for all the stuff
that's going on.
Because I could go on about loads of stuff that's going on.
But yeah, go and have a look in there if you're not up to date and then we'll
keep posting things in there as well.
Okay, ladies.
Thanks very much, everybody.
You've really enjoyed that.
Lots of information for me to take on board.
Thank you so much.
Oh, yeah, it's a great advice as well.
Lord knows.
Brilliant.
Nice meeting.
So nice to talk to everyone.
Oh, it is, isn't it?
Oh, well, good night, ladies.
And we'll catch up in group tomorrow.
I'm in group tomorrow.